Guide to the School of Law Records, 1914-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Deans Papers, 1929-1999, undated, 95 Linear Feet (63.5 boxes)
  - Dean Elvin Jack Latty, 1940-1968, undated (bulk 1958-1966)
    - Faculty Salaries, undated (Box 26)
    - Family Correspondence, 1963-1965, undated (Box 26)
    - Fifth Decade Program, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
    - Financial Statement, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
    - Foreign Material, Duke Law Library, 1959-1960, undated (Box 26)
    - Foreign Students, 1963 (Box 26)
    - Foundation Press, Inc., 1961 (Box 26)
    - Foundations, 1959-1960 (Box 26)
    - Foundations and Governmental Support, 1963-1964 (Box 26)
    - Fraternities, 1958-1960 (Box 26)
    - Fundraising Ideas, 1958-1961 (Box 26)
    - G Correspondence, 1959-1965 (Box 26)
    - Gantt, Samuel F., 1960, undated (Box 26)
    - Gerontology, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Gift Prospects, 1966-1967, undated (Box 26)
    - Graduate Study, 1961-1962 (Box 26)
    - Graduates, 1962-1963, undated (Box 26)
    - Graduate Study Program, 1959-1961 (Box 26)
    - Gross, Dr. Paul, 1959-1960 (Box 26)
    - H Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 26)
    - Hanft, Frank William, 1963 (Box 26)
    - Hanna, Professor John, 1960-1961 (Box 26)
    - Hart, President Deryl, 1960-1963, undated (Box 26)
    - Herring, Vice-President H.J., 1958-1960 (Box 26)
    - Homecoming, 1959-1961, undated (Box 26)
    - Housing, 1959-1961, undated (Box 26)
    - Imprest Cash, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
    - Inquiries, Oriental and African, 1960-1962 (Box 26)
    - Inspection, Duke Law School February 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 26)
    - Institutes Ideas, 1961-1962 (Box 26)
    - Insurance Law Institute, 1959 (Box 26)
    - Inter-American Law Institute, 1959 (Box 26)
    - International Commission of Jurist, 1957-1959 (Box 26)
    - International Congress of Comparitave Law (Brussels), 1957-1958 (Box 26)
    - International Court of Justice, 1960 (Box 26)
    - Intramurals, 1964 (Box 26)
    - Introduction to Business Administration, Frampton and Little Brown, 1958-1961, undated (Box 26)
    - Israeli company Law (Israels, Abrams, Latty), 1957-1960, undated (Box 26)
    - J Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 26)
    - Joint Degree, JD-MD, 1963-1966, undated (Box 26)
    - Journal of Legal Education, 1958-1963 (Box 26)
    - Judicial Conference of the Fourth Circuit, 1959 (Box 26)
    - K Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 26)
    - Knight, Douglas Maitland, 1962-1965 (Box 26)
    - Kramer, Robert,1949-1961 (Box 27)
    - L Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 27)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1957-1964 (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1961-1966 (Box 27)
    - Law Day, 1959-1966, undated (3 folders) (Box 27)
    - Law Day Clippings, 1966, undated (Box 27)
    - Law Deans Rating of Law Schools, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Law Journal, 1962-1966, undated (Box 27)
    - Law School Admission Test, 1958-1960 (Box 27)
    - Law School News, 1960-1961, undated (Box 27)
    - Law School Statistics, 1963 (Box 27)
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 1958-1960 (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Legal Aid Clinics, National Council on, 1960 (Box 27)
    - Legal- Medical Course File, 1959-1960 (Box 27)
    - Legal Research, 1966, undated (Box 27)
    - Letters to Men Requesting Lists of Top Firms in their Area, 1961 (Box 27)
    - Liacouras, Peter, 1959-1963 (Box 27)
    - Lists, Students Enrolled, 1960 (Box 27)
    - Loans, New Students, 1965-1966, undated (Box 27)
    - Loans, General, 1966-1967 (Box 27)
    - Loan Guaranty Plan, 1962-1963, undated (Box 27)
    - Long Range Planning, Law School, 1958-1959, undated (Box 27)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1959-1962, undated (Box 27)
    - Loyalty Fund, 1961, undated (Box 27)
    - M Correspondence, 1957-1963 (Box 27)
    - McClure, Dr. Wallace, 1958-1962, undated (Box 27)
    - Maggs, Douglas B., 1957-1963, undated (Box 27)
    - Matching Gifts Program, 1964 (Box 27)
    - Meade, Charles Houston, 1960-1963, undated (Box 27)
    - Memorandums to Law Faculty, 1958-1965 (2 folders) (Box 27)
    - Merrill, David N., 1964 (Box 27)
    - Midsemester Examinations 1960, 1960, undated (Box 27)
    - Miller, Arthur, 1960-1961 (Box 27)
    - Minutes of Faculty Meetings, 1958-1964 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous, 1964, undated (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1957-1965, undated (7 folders) (Box 28)
    - Moot Court, 1958-1961, undated (Box 28)
    - Mordecai Society, 1958-1965 (Box 28)
    - Mortality Reports, 1960 (Box 28)
    - N Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 28)
    - Nathan Burkan Memorial competition, 1958-1961, undated (Box 28)
    - New Building, Clippings, 1963 (Box 28)
    - New Building, Dedication Correspondence, 1959-1963 (5 folders) (Box 28)
    - New Building, Law Buildings in the Southern States 1940, 1940 (Box 28)
    - New Building, Law Library (Miles O. Price Consultant), 1961-1962 (Box 28)
    - New Building, Planning and Construction, 1947,1956-1963 (6 folders) (Box 29)
    - New Building, Specification Book, Inserted Letter, 1960 (Box 29)
    - New Building, Specifications, A Building for the School of Law, Duke University book, 1960 (Box 29)
    - New York Corporation Revision, 1957-1959 (Box 29)
    - Nixon File, 1958-1961, undated (Box 29)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, General, 1959-1965 (3 folders) (Box 29)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Committee on New Business Corporation Act, 1957-1960 (Box 29)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Continuing Legal Education Committee, 1960-1963 (Box 29)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Institutes, 1956-1965 (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - North Carolina General Court Legal Project, 1961-1962 (Box 29)
    - Orientation Program in American Law, 1965-1967 (2 folders) (Box 29)
    - Operation Breakthrough, 1966-1967 (Box 30)
    - Orientation, 1959-1964, undated (Box 30)
    - Other Schools Institutes, Conferences, 1959-1960 (Box 30)
    - P Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 30)
    - Patent Law, 1960-1961, undated (Box 30)
    - Patent (U.S. - International) Research Grant, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Payroll, Student Monthly, 1961 (Box 30)
    - Personal Correspondence, 1953, 1959-1965 (9 Folders) (Box 30)
    - Personal Correspondence, Alumni, 1960-1962 (2 folders) (Box 30)
    - Personal Correspondence, Family, 1960-1963 (Box 30)
    - Personnel, 1958-1962 (Box 30)
    - Peterson, Courtland, 1958-1959 (Box 30)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1959-1960 (Box 30)
    - Placement, 1959-1962 (Box 30)
    - Placement Brochure, 1960 (Box 30)
    - Placement File (the Dean's Office File), 1959-1960 (Box 30)
    - Placement General File, 1959-1962 (Box 30)
    - Placement General, 1959-1961 (Box 30)
    - Placement Inquiries, 1959, undated (Box 30)
    - Placement Interview Schedules, 1961, undated (Box 31)
    - Placement, National Assocation of Placement Officers, 1960 (Box 31)
    - Plans and Projects, 1958-1960, undated (Box 31)
    - Poisson, John Paul, 1965, undated (Box 31)
    - Porvaznik, Paul robert, 1960-1962, undated (Box 31)
    - Pre-Legal Advisors, 1959, undated (Box 31)
    - Pre-Legal Readings, 1952-1960, undated (Box 31)
    - Practising Law Institute, 1960 (Box 31)
    - Price, Miles O., 1958-1963 (Box 31)
    - Prizes, 1958-1962 (Box 31)
    - Professional Affairs Committee, 1963, undated (Box 31)
    - Programs, National Defenders Project, General, 1965-1970, undated (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Prolocuter, 1957-1962, undated (Box 31)
    - Prospective Law Teachers, 1951, 1957-1960 (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Prospective Law Teachers, B List, 1958-1962, undated (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - R Correspondence and Files, 1957-1962, undated (Box 31)
    - Receipts, 1962-1963 (Box 31)
    - Recruitment, 1958-1961, undated (Box 31)
    - Research and Writing, 1959-1960, undated (Box 31)
    - Registration File, 1960 (Box 31)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1960-1961 (Box 31)
    - Richardson Foundation, 1958-1961 (Box 31)
    - Reserve Officers Training Corps, 1966 (Box 31)
    - Rotondi, 1959, undated (Box 31)
    - Rule of Law Center, 1958-1963, undated (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Russell Sage Foundation, 1960 (Box 31)
    - S Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 31)
    - Salaries, 1958-1965, undated (Box 31)
    - Schmitthoff Proposal, 1951-1953, 1957-1958 (Box 31)
    - Scholarship Awards, 1958-1961 (Box 31)
    - Scholarships, Correspondence, 1954-1961 (Box 31)
    - Scholarship Gifts, 1962 (Box 31)
    - Securities and Exchange commission, 1961-1963, undated (Box 31)
    - Small Business Administration, 1959-1961 (Box 31)
    - Small Business Institute, 1958-1959 (Box 31)
    - Southeastern Regional Law Teachers conference, 1962-1965 (Box 31)
    - Southern Railway System, 1961-1962 (Box 31)
    - Speakers, 1957-1963 (2 folders) (Box 31)
    - Speaking Engagements, 1960-1962, undated (Box 32)
    - Speeches Received, 1957-1962, undated (Box 32)
    - Stanford University, 1962 (Box 32)
    - State Farm Insurance, 1960-1963, undated (Box 32)
    - Statistics, 1959-1961 (Box 32)
    - Stewart, Carl, Assistant to the Dean, 1960 (Box 32)
    - Summer Institute of Lawyers, 1961, undated (Box 32)
    - Summer Internship Reports of Law Students, 1965-1966 (Box 32)
    - Supreme Court of Nevada, 1962 (Box 32)
    - Symposiums, Meetings, Conferences to be held at Law School, 1965, undated (Box 32)
    - T Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 32)
    - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association, college Retirement Equities Fund, 1959 (Box 32)
    - Tenth School Law Conference, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Tener, Jeffrey Booth, 1962-1965, undated (Box 32)
    - Traffic Commission, 1957-1962 (Box 32)
    - Trustees, Duke University, 1958-1960, undated (Box 32)
    - Trustee, Faculty and President Selection Committee, 1962 (Box 32)
    - Tuition, Duke Law School and Others, undated (Box 32)
    - United Nations Summer Program, 1961 (Box 32)
    - University Council, 1959-1961, undated (Box 32)
    - V Correspondence and Files, 1959-1961 (Box 32)
    - Visiting Committee, 1963-1965 (Box 32)
    - Visits to Other Law Schools (By E.R. Latty), 1957 (Box 32)
    - W Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 32)
    - Wadlington, Professor Walter J., 1962 (Box 32)
    - West Publishing Company, Law School News, 1961-1964 (Box 32)
    - Whitlock, James Coit Jr., 1962-1964, undated (Box 32)
    - Williamson, Hugh H., 1964, undated (Box 32)
    - Willis Smith Prize, 1957-1960 (Box 32)
    - Wills Contest, 1958-1962, undated (Box 32)
    - Wilson, Dr. Robert, 1959-1961 (Box 32)
  - Dean F. Hodge O'Neal, 1965-1968, undated.
    F. Hodge O'Neal was dean of the law school from 1966 to 1968.
    - Air Pollution, 1967-1968, undated (Box 32)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Annual Meeting, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Round Table Council on Business Associations, 1965-1968 (Box 32)
    - Baade, Hans W., 1967 (Box 32)
    - Bolich, William Bryan, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
    - Brainerd Currie Lecture, 1966-1968, undated (Box 32)
    - Bryson, Edwin Constant, 1966-1967 (Box 32)
    - Budget, 1966-1967 (Box 32)
    - Building Plans, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Cannon, Edward L., 1966 (Box 32)
    - Colorado Bar Association Speech, 1966-1967 (Box 32)
    - Commencement, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, Personal, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Defense Research Institute, inc., 1966 (Box 32)
    - Estate Planning, 1967, undated (Box 32)
    - Evaluation Reports (Regarding Law School Courses), 1966-1967 (2 folders) (Box 32)
    - Expenses, Entering Students, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Faculty, Tenured, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Fifth Decade, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
    - Georgia State Bar Speech, 1966, undated (Box 32)
    - Insurance, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Joint Degree, J.D. - M.D. 1966-1968, undated (Box 32)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
    - Law Dames, 1966-1967 (Box 32)
    - Law Day, 1966-1969 (Box 32)
    - Law Journal, 1966-1968 (Box 33)
    - Legal Research Program, 1967-1968 (Box 33)
    - Maintenance, 1965-1966 (Box 33)
    - Moot Court, 1968 (Box 33)
    - Moot Court and Deans Cup, 1967, undated (Box 33)
    - Mordecai Society, 1967-1968, undated (Box 33)
    - National Defenders Project, 1966-1968, undated (Box 33)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1966-1968 (Box 33)
    - Personnel, 1967-1968 (Box 33)
    - Programs, OEO Proposal, 1966-1968, undated (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Rules of Duke Law School, 1966-1967, undated (Box 33)
    - Southwestern University Speech, 1966-1967 (Box 33)
  - Dean A. Kenneth Pye, 1968-1973, undated
    A Kenneth Pye served as dean of the law school from 1968-1970 and again from 1973-1976. Pye was the University Chancellor between his two terms as dean. There may be some documentation within this subseries from his time as chancellor and his other term as dean.
    - Air Pollution, Triangle Universities Consortium on Air Pollution, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Alumni, 1970, undated (Box 33)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - American Bar Association, Commission on Campus Government and Student Dissent, 1969-1970, undated (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - American Bar Association Studies, 1970 (Box 33)
    - American Law Institute, 1965 (Box 33)
    - Baade, Hans W., 1968-1970 (Box 33)
    - Bolich, William Bryan, 1968-1970 (Box 33)
    - Bradway, Jophn Saeger, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Building Plans, 1970 (Box 33)
    - Clinical Program, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Committees Faculty, 1970 (Box 33)
    - Committees, Students and Faculty, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Contest, 1970 (Box 33)
    - Brainerd Currie, 1969-1971 (Box 33)
    - Delta Theta Phi, 1969 (Box 33)
    - Discrimination, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1969 (Box 33)
    - Faculty, Sabbatical Leave, 1969 (Box 33)
    - Fifth Decade Campaign, 1969-1971 (Box 33)
    - Gift Programs, 1968-1971 (Box 33)
    - Grading, 1970 (Box 33)
    - International Studies, 1970 (Box 33)
    - Joint Degree, J.D. - M.B.A., 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Joint Degree, M.D. - J.D., 1968-1970 (Box 33)
    - Judicial Degree, 1970 (Box 33)
    - Judicial Board Code, 1969-1970, undated (Box 33)
    - Krueger, Robert, 1968-1972, undated (Box 33)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Law Dames, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Law Day, 1968-1970, 1975, undated (Box 33)
    - Law Examiners, 1969 (Box 33)
    - Law Journal, 1968-1970 (Box 33)
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 1970-1973, undated (2 folders) (Box 33)
    - Legal Research, 1968-1969, undated (Box 33)
    - Library Rules, 1969 (Box 34)
    - Loyalty Fund, General, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - Maintenance, 1968-1969 (Box 34)
    - Moot Court, Deans Cup, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - Mordecai Society, 1970 (Box 34)
    - National Defenders Project, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - North Carolina Association of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1970-1972 (Box 34)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1968-1970 (Box 34)
    - North Carolina Legal Services Association, 1970 (Box 34)
    - Order of the Coif, 1970 (Box 34)
    - Orientation, 1969-1970, undated (Box 34)
    - Placement, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Policy, 1968 (Box 34)
    - Speakers, 1970 (Box 34)
    - Task Force on Apprehension and Suppression, 1968-1970, undated (Box 34)
    - University Hearing Committee, Allen Building Occupation, 1968-1969, undated (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - University Hearing Committee, Symposium Disruption, 1968-1969, undated (Box 34)
  - Dean Joseph P. Sneed, 1954-1973, undated (bulk 1971-1973)
    Joseph Sneed was dean of the law school from 1971-1973.
    - Admissions, Minority Groups, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
    - Air Pollution, Triangle Universities Consoritum on Air Pollution, 1971-1973 (Box 34)
    - Alumni, General, 1971 (Box 34)
    - Alumni, General, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Alumni Gifts, 1972-1973 (Box 34)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1954-1955, 1971-1973 (Box 34)
    - American Bar Association, Center for Administrative Justice, 1972-1973 (Box 34)
    - American Bar Association Studies, 1969-1973, undated (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1971-1975 (2 folders) (Box 34)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Curriculum Study Project, 1971 (Box 34)
    - Baade, Hans W., 1971-1972 (Box 34)
    - Benefits, Students and Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
    - Bolich, William Bryan, 1970-1972, undated (Box 34)
    - Bryson, Edwin Constant, 1971 (Box 34)
    - Building Plans, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
    - Sneed: Class Census Forms, 1971-1973 (Box 34)
    - Character Review of Candidates for Law School, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
    - Clinical Programs, Council for Legal Education for Professional Responsibility, 1971-1972, undated (3 folders) (Box 35)
    - Commencement Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 35)
    - Committee on Aging, 1971-1973 (Box 35)
    - Committees, 1971-1973 (Box 35)
    - Committees, Curriculum, 1971-1972, undated (Box 35)
    - Committees, Faculty Appointments, Tenure, 1971-1972, undated (Box 35)
    - Committees, Student - Faculty, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - Consultants and Fees, Faculty and Staff, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Contests, 1971-1973, undated (Box 35)
    - Council on Legal Education for Professional Responsibility, 1968-1971, undated (6 folders) (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, Chancellor, 1971-1973 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, Counsel, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, General, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, President, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, Provost, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Criminal Justice, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - Currie, Brainerd, 1971-1973 (Box 35)
    - Deferred Tuition, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Educational Administration Committee, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Enrollment Statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - Environmental Law, 1971-1972 (Box 35)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Faculty, General, 1972, undated (Box 35)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1971-1972, undated (Box 35)
    - Faculty, Sabbatical Requests, 1971-1972, undated (Box 35)
    - Financial Aid, 1970-1972 (Box 36)
    - Financial Aid Policy, 1967, 1970-1972, undated (2 folders) (Box 36)
    - Ford Foundation Common Problems Research Corporation, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Gift Prospects, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Grading, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Heating and Air Conditioning, 1970-1971 (Box 36)
    - Inquiries on Law Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Institute of Policy Sciences Faculty Prospects, 1972 (Box 36)
    - Joint Degree, J.D. - M.D., 1971 (Box 36)
    - Joint Degree, 3/3 Program, 1971-1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Judicial Board Code, 19767, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1971 (Box 36)
    - Law Dames, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Law Day, 1971-1973, undated (Box 36)
    - Law Forum (Speakers), 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Law Journal, 1971-1973 (Box 36)
    - Law Schools, Materials Relating to, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Legal Research Program, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Legal Services, 1971-1973, undated (Box 36)
    - Library, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Life Income Fund, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Limited Courses, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Loyalty Fund, Donors Letters, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Loyalty Fund Statistics, 1971-1973 (Box 36)
    - Maintenance, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Moot Court and Dean's Cup, 1971-1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Mordecai Society, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - National Center for State Courts, 1971, undated (Box 36)
    - National Endowment of Humanities, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - New York Bar, 1972 (Box 36)
    - New York Bar, undated (Box 36)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Bar Foundation, 1971-1972, undated (Box 36)
    - North Carolina Law Examiners, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Order of the Coif, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Orientation, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Phi Alpha Delta, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Placement, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Public Policy, M.A. Degree, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Public Policy Program, 1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Questions, Law School, 1971-1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Retirement, Faculty and Staff, 1965, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Salaries, Faculty and Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 36)
    - Third Year Practice, 1971-1972, undated (Box 36)
    - Trial Advocacy Club, 1972 (Box 37)
    - Tuition, 1972 (Box 37)
    - University Planning Committee, 1971-1972, undated (4 folders) (Box 37)
    - University Planning Committee, Professional School Subcommittee, 1971-1972, undated (Box 37)
    - Xerox, 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - Dean A. Kenneth Pye, 1970-1977, undated.
    - Accreditation, American Bar Association, 1975-1977, undated (Box 37)
    - Admission Policy, 1974-1975 (Box 37)
    - Admissions, 1974 (Box 37)
    - Admissions, 1976, undated (Box 37)
    - Admissions, Automatic Offers, 1975 (Box 37)
    - Admissions, Minorities, 1973-1974, undated (Box 37)
    - Admissions, Minorities, 1973-1975, undated (Box 37)
    - Admissions, Recommendations, 1974-1976 (Box 37)
    - Admissions Statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 37)
    - Admissions Statistics, 1976 (Box 37)
    - Affirmative Action, undated (Box 37)
    - Alumni, General, Council, Weekend, Letters, Etc., 1974 (Box 37)
    - Alumni, General, Meetings, Weekend, Letters, Etc., 1973 (Box 37)
    - Alumni, General, Meetings, Weekend, Letters, Etc., 1976 (Box 37)
    - Alumni Gifts and Contributions, 1973-1976 (Box 37)
    - Alumni Lists, undated (Box 37)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1973 (Box 37)
    - American Bar Association, Accreditation Standards, 1975-1976 (2 folders) (Box 37)
    - American Bar Association, Commission on a National Institute of Justice, 1973-1974, undated (5 of 7 folders) (Box 37)
    - American Bar Association, Commission on a National Institute of Justice, 1973-1974, undated (folders 6 and 7 of 7) (Box 38)
    - American Bar Association, Law School Studies, 1973-1976, undated (3 folders) (Box 38)
    - American Bar Association, Section of Administrative Law Administrative Process Committee, 1969-1974 (3 folders) (Box 38)
    - American Bar Association, Section of Legal Education and Admissions to the Bar, Consultants Monthly Report, 1972-1975 (Box 38)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1973 (Box 38)
    - American Law Institute and American Bar Assocation Joint Committee on Continuing Legal Education, 1970-1975 (Box 38)
    - Articles Published, 1963, 1969-1976, undated (2 folders) (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Accreditation Committee, 1973 (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Annual Meeting, 1973-1974, undated (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Annual Meeting, 1975 (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Committees, 1976-1977 (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Executive Committee, 1973 (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Executive Committee Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Faculty Roster, 1976 (1 of 3 folders) (Box 38)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Faculty Roster, 1976 (folders 2 and 3 of 3) (Box 39)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Fall Roster, 1976 (3 folders) (Box 39)
    - Association of American Law Schools, General, 1970-1973 (Box 39)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Study of Scholars Privileges, 1973 (Box 39)
    - B Cases, 1975, 1977 (Box 39)
    - Barristers, 1974-1976 (Box 39)
    - Basketball Controversy, 1974-1975, undated (Box 39)
    - Benefits, Faculty and Staff, 1973-1976 (Box 39)
    - Board of Trustees, Report to Academic Affairs, 1975 (Box 39)
    - Board of Visitors Meeting, 1976 (Box 39)
    - Bolich, William Bryan, 1973, undated (Box 39)
    - Buckley Ammendment, 1974-1945, undated (Box 39)
    - Building Plans, 1973-1975 (Box 39)
    - Bureau of Prisons, 1976 (Box 39)
    - Calendar, Proposed for 1973-1974, 1973 (Box 39)